<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-10T13:51:12+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">We Have Nothing to Fear But Fear of Failing Itself</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/04/we-have-nothing-to-fear-but-fear-of-failing-itself.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We Have Nothing to Fear But Fear of Failing Itself" /><published>2023-03-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-03-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/03/04/we-have-nothing-to-fear-but-fear-of-failing-itself</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/03/04/we-have-nothing-to-fear-but-fear-of-failing-itself.html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/0.jpg" alt="" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Amy Likes Spiders</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/27/amy-likes-spiders.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Amy Likes Spiders" /><published>2023-02-27T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-27T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/27/amy-likes-spiders</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/27/amy-likes-spiders.html"><![CDATA[<p>Amy told me she likes spiders.<br />
She has even shown me one of them.<br />
Icky, wriggly, hairy, ugly spiders!<br />
But I’m still friends with her.<br />
<br />
Amy never told anyone about her spiders.<br />
She only wanted me to know this.<br />
I don’t really get why she likes them.<br />
But I’m still friends with her.<br />
<br />
Amy has a lot of friends.<br />
She can’t talk to them about her spiders.<br />
She’s afraid they will not like that.<br />
But I’m still friends with her.<br />
<br />
She has other hobbies we can both enjoy.<br />
She keeps this one private.<br />
This one doesn’t hurt anyone.<br />
<br />
I know she trusts me.<br />
Her trust means a lot to me.<br />
My world is better with her in it.<br />
<br />
And I’m not gonna tell anyone.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy told me she likes spiders. She has even shown me one of them. Icky, wriggly, hairy, ugly spiders! But I’m still friends with her. Amy never told anyone about her spiders. She only wanted me to know this. I don’t really get why she likes them. But I’m still friends with her. Amy has a lot of friends. She can’t talk to them about her spiders. She’s afraid they will not like that. But I’m still friends with her. She has other hobbies we can both enjoy. She keeps this one private. This one doesn’t hurt anyone. I know she trusts me. Her trust means a lot to me. My world is better with her in it. And I’m not gonna tell anyone.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Special Place in Heaven</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/26/a-special-place-in-heaven.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Special Place in Heaven" /><published>2023-02-26T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-26T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/26/a-special-place-in-heaven</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/26/a-special-place-in-heaven.html"><![CDATA[<p>If you wait for long enough,<br />
You will get what you deserve.<br />
Just stay silent, don’t rebuff—<br />
Heaven’s got a place reserved.<br />
<br />
Place where only patient go.<br />
Those who do anticipate.<br />
Place where you and I belong—<br />
Those who are deliberate.<br />
<br />
Sometimes things just need to pass,<br />
Sometimes waiting is the prize.<br />
Other times they’d better last.<br />
No one’s waiting for demise.<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you wait for long enough, You will get what you deserve. Just stay silent, don’t rebuff— Heaven’s got a place reserved. Place where only patient go. Those who do anticipate. Place where you and I belong— Those who are deliberate. Sometimes things just need to pass, Sometimes waiting is the prize. Other times they’d better last. No one’s waiting for demise.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Illusion</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/24/illusion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Illusion" /><published>2023-02-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/24/illusion</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/24/illusion.html"><![CDATA[<p>Even texture effects submit to the illusion of transparence<br />
Disorder leading to indefinite confusion of the essence<br />
What reflects the human nature in an intricate complexity<br />
Is what’s bleeding through the pages with an uttermost necessity<br />
<br />
Puzzled by the mesmerizing ignorance of the enlightened ones<br />
Who pick up their pens and pencils like the soldiers who pick up their guns<br />
Praying to the traumatizing goddesses who terrorize their flock while<br />
Preying on inferiors who fall under their mock and foul hostile smile<br />
<br />
Meaningless calamities that occupy their minds<br />
Form dissolves in substance, gets lost between the lines<br />
Is there any reason for you to look inside?<br />
Just to find the horrors created by your mind.<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even texture effects submit to the illusion of transparence Disorder leading to indefinite confusion of the essence What reflects the human nature in an intricate complexity Is what’s bleeding through the pages with an uttermost necessity Puzzled by the mesmerizing ignorance of the enlightened ones Who pick up their pens and pencils like the soldiers who pick up their guns Praying to the traumatizing goddesses who terrorize their flock while Preying on inferiors who fall under their mock and foul hostile smile Meaningless calamities that occupy their minds Form dissolves in substance, gets lost between the lines Is there any reason for you to look inside? Just to find the horrors created by your mind.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Byte Array</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/23/byte-array.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Byte Array" /><published>2023-02-23T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/23/byte-array</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/23/byte-array.html"><![CDATA[<p>Oh, trans-humanists, rejoice—<br />
It’s your time to make a choice!<br />
This is not a chance to miss,<br />
You can be in endless bliss!<br />
<br />
Never heard before breakthrough<br />
Now available to you.<br />
Load your mind into device,<br />
For a reasonable price.<br />
<br />
All the gimmicks you can think,<br />
Once you press a key to sync.<br />
You won’t need to eat or sleep.<br />
Well, and batteries are cheap!<br />
<br />
All the knowledge in the world,<br />
Solitaire, Excel and Word,<br />
E-mail, Internet, and more.<br />
Work or play, you won’t get bored!<br />
<br />
What? Your body? Worry not!<br />
It will not be left to rot.<br />
It will have its application<br />
For the human population.<br />
<br />
Just don’t think too much, okay?<br />
And just double tap to pay.<br />
You are only step away<br />
From becoming byte array.<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, trans-humanists, rejoice— It’s your time to make a choice! This is not a chance to miss, You can be in endless bliss! Never heard before breakthrough Now available to you. Load your mind into device, For a reasonable price. All the gimmicks you can think, Once you press a key to sync. You won’t need to eat or sleep. Well, and batteries are cheap! All the knowledge in the world, Solitaire, Excel and Word, E-mail, Internet, and more. Work or play, you won’t get bored! What? Your body? Worry not! It will not be left to rot. It will have its application For the human population. Just don’t think too much, okay? And just double tap to pay. You are only step away From becoming byte array.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Status Quo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/22/status-quo.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Status Quo" /><published>2023-02-22T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/22/status-quo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/22/status-quo.html"><![CDATA[<p>Nothing ventured, nothing gained;<br />
Nothing done and nothing planned;<br />
Nothing said and nothing thought;<br />
Nothing taken, nothing brought.<br />
<br />
Doing anything? No thanks.<br />
Doing means that I will fail.<br />
Doing things requires change.<br />
Doing means things rearrange.<br />
<br />
I would rather stay in place.<br />
Doing nothing is okay.<br />
Stable is a place to be.<br />
I enjoy it, can’t you see?<br />
<br />
You can go and chase your dream,<br />
If it makes you feel supreme.<br />
I will be where I belong,<br />
Where I have been all along.<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing ventured, nothing gained; Nothing done and nothing planned; Nothing said and nothing thought; Nothing taken, nothing brought. Doing anything? No thanks. Doing means that I will fail. Doing things requires change. Doing means things rearrange. I would rather stay in place. Doing nothing is okay. Stable is a place to be. I enjoy it, can’t you see? You can go and chase your dream, If it makes you feel supreme. I will be where I belong, Where I have been all along.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Place Where I Don’t Exist</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/20/place-where-i-don't-exist.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Place Where I Don’t Exist" /><published>2023-02-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2023-02-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/20/place-where-i-don&apos;t-exist</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/20/place-where-i-don&apos;t-exist.html"><![CDATA[<p>Is it warmer in the place where I don’t exist?<br />
Does the sun shine brighter there?<br />
If it is, then what makes it so?<br />
<br />
Why do you look in the mirror?<br />
What are you hoping to see?<br />
Who’s that stranger staring back?<br />
What if you switched places with them?<br />
<br />
Is your reality a distorted reflection<br />
Of something that’s meant to be?<br />
Or is it as real as the text on the screen<br />
That was typed for amusement only?<br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it warmer in the place where I don’t exist? Does the sun shine brighter there? If it is, then what makes it so? Why do you look in the mirror? What are you hoping to see? Who’s that stranger staring back? What if you switched places with them? Is your reality a distorted reflection Of something that’s meant to be? Or is it as real as the text on the screen That was typed for amusement only?]]></summary></entry></feed>